原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译：草草 Reginamoon 王大可 木浅薰 一点都不酷
翻译：某羽 Lynn_宁   校对：某羽 木浅薰
时间轴：霜露   壬虚浪影   今
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第十五集
最新海外影视剧下载
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits
这不是《西部世界》
This isn't "Westworld."
-我不能使她人性化  -我只是希望你
- I can't make her human. - I'm just asking you
给她点同情心
to give her a little compassion.
我不知道该怎么做
Well, I don't know how to do that.
我刚和卡莉・唐纳休通过电话
Just got off the phone with Carly Donahue.
她把我们解雇了  唐娜
She fired us, Donna.
这不是你的错
This isn't your fault.
-你又想不到  -没事  我得回家去了
- You couldn't have known. - It's okay, I just need to go.
你以工作导致威胁生命的健康问题为由提出过控告
You filed a complaint alleging life-threatening health problems,
而我希望帮助你获得你应得的赔偿
and I wanna help you get the compensation that you deserve.
但即便我想起诉那帮混蛋  我也不能
Even if I wanted to sue those bastards, I can't.
我们能解除那些保密协议
We can shatter those NDAs.
需要我做什么
What do I have to do?
你是否想利用此案
I wanna know if you're using this case
重回皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所
to get back to Pearson Specter.
因为你告诉我你还在皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所时
You said Pearson Specter would never take on
他们绝不会接这种案子
a case like this when you were there before.
我们接这个案子  让我能进律师协会
We brought the suit so that I could get into the Bar.
-一个亿  -并公开承认犯错
- 100 million. - With an admission of guilt.
好啊  合同给我签
Sure, where do I sign?
我可以直接付给你的客户
I'm willing to cut your clients a check
让他们的生活焕然一新
that'll change their lives
而你却笨得看不到这点
and you're too stupid to see it.
你到底要不要为你曾经做过的负责
Are you ready to take responsibility or not?
你认为你偷了赛德尔公司的技术
You think I won't go after you
我不呢个追究你盗窃吗
for stealing from Seidel's company?
我才不在乎他的婚姻
I don't give a shit about his marriage.
他不肯出面
The reason he hasn't come forward has nothing to do
根本不是因为他的婚姻
with his marriage.
你不是因为结婚了才想低调处理此事
You didn't have to keep this quiet because you're married.
你是因为牵涉其中才这么做
You kept it quiet because you're in on it.
我的员工会因为我而失业
My employees are gonna lose their jobs because of me.
我们得把官司打下去
We need to keep this suit going.
你不仅要给迈克安排面试
You're not just getting Mike an interview,
还要说服每个投反对票的人
you're gonna block anyone who tries to vote no.
我们律师协会见
See you at the Bar.
斯塔摩斯先生  你来做什么
Mr. Stamos. What are you doing here?
我想把病例的授权拿给你
I wanted to get you the authorization to our medical records.
谢谢
Thanks.
但是  你大老远来
But, uh, you didn't come all the way down here
不是为了送份文件吧
just to hand me some paperwork.
是啊  我是来问问
You're right. I came to find out
我们的案子怎么样了
what's going on with our case.
应该很快就会有消息了
We should hear something soon.
-你怎么能知道  -因为哈维这会儿
- How can you know that? - 'Cause Harvey is negotiating
就在跟詹姆斯・帕默谈判
with James Palmer as we speak.
什么意思
What do you mean?
为什么是哈维・斯佩克特去谈判
Why is Harvey Specter negotiating this?
我们拉上他时我就说过
I told you when we took him on,
他是本市最好的谈判人
he's the best negotiator in the city.
我不在乎他是谁
I don't care who he is.
是你来找我的  我信任的是你
You're the one that came to me. You're the one I trusted.
我知道  但我们有红白脸的策略
I know that, but we've got a good cop/bad cop strategy
-好抬高报价  -报价
- to get the offer up. - An offer?
你没提什么报价
You didn't tell me there's an offer.
-因为事情...  -多少
- That's because things are - How much?
现在的数字是一亿
The number on the table is a hundred.
但我们想拿到更多
But we're hoping to get a lot more.
天呐  一亿美元吗  接受啊
Jesus Christ, 100 million? Take it.
我知道这看上去是不少
I know it seems like a lot of money--
-这的确不少  -但要150个
- It is a lot of money. - Not when you have to
患了癌症的人均分就不那么多了
split it between 150 men who have cancer.
随你怎么算  罗斯先生
Do all the math you want, Mr. Ross,
但一亿美元比零多多了
but 100 million is a hell of lot better than zero,
而我们以前得到的就是零
which is what we've been walking around with.
斯塔摩斯先生  你得信任我
Mr. Stamos, you have to trust me.
我们心里有数  我不会让你失望的
We know what we're doing and I am not gonna let you down.
好吧
Fine.
你采取你的红白脸策略吧
You do your good cop/bad cop thing.
但如果那数字两天内还不升高
But if that number doesn't go up in the next two days,
我就会叫大家接受已有的报价
I'm telling my guys to take the offer that's on the table.
本杰明  真・唐娜已经可以了
Benjamin, the Donna is ready.
什么意思
What do you mean she's ready?
我是说  五分钟前  她向我表达了共情
I mean, five minutes ago she expressed empathy to me.
但之前不好使的
But it wasn't working before.
我还以为不可能成功了
I was convinced it never would.
我不知道你做了什么  但你说它可以
I don't know what you did, but you said it could
自我学习  它做到了
learn from itself, and that's exactly what happened.
天呐  或许我真是个天才
Oh, my God. Maybe I really am a genius.
是啊
Yeah, maybe you are.
那幸好我没把这个丢掉
Well, then it's a good thing I didn't throw this away.
-这是什么  -我列了张单子
- What's this? - I've compiled a list
写了所有这五年来对此类产品
of everybody who's invested in products like this
投过资的人
in the last five years.
很好  但我们不需要这个
That's great, but we're not gonna need this.
为什么
Why not?
因为真・唐娜的特别之处是我
Because the thing that makes the Donna special is me.
所以我们得找认识我的投资者
Which means we need to look into investors who know me.
是啊  没错  没人比哈维更了解你了
Yes, correct, and nobody knows you better than Harvey.
你觉得他会代我们找人吗
Do you think he'll make calls on our behalf?
他会的  但我不会去求他
He would, but I'm not gonna ask him to do that
因为我希望他的客户看到
because I want his clients to see this
这是我的主意  不是他的
as coming from me and not him.
那我们接下来怎么办
Then what's the next step?
你接下来要做好展示它的准备
The next step for you is get ready to present that thing,
因为我会为我们安排会面的
because I'm going to get us some meetings.
太棒了
Boom shakalaka.
你知道现在几点了吗
Do you have any idea what time it is?
知道  但等不了了
I do, but it couldn't wait.
瑞秋呢
Where's Rachel?
她去父母家了  怎么了
She's at her parents' house. Why?
因为我有消息
Because I have some news
-她会想听听的  -什么事
- and she's gonna wanna hear it. - What is it?
我们成了  你进了
We got it. You're in.
-你能当律师了  -什么  怎么说
- You're going to be a lawyer. - What? How?
赛德尔也有份  他收了钱
Seidel was in on it. He got paid.
我有证据  所以我们不用再去
And I got proof. Which means we don't have to
拉低极速的股价了
worry about tanking Velocity's stock anymore.
天呐  难以置信
Oh, my God. I can't believe it.
-我要当律师了  -是啊
- I'm going to be a lawyer. - I know.
但有个麻烦
There's just one thing.
帕默发现我们在跟赛德尔合作了
Palmer figured out that we're doing this with Seidel.
除非我们撤诉
And unless we drop the lawsuit,
否则他要告我们合谋
he's gonna come after us for collusion.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
不  这不行
No, this is bullshit.
我不会放弃那些矿工的
I'm not giving up on those miners.
-你必须放弃  -并非如此
- You have to. - No, I don't.
-迈克  -听着  我们唯一
- Mike. - Look, the only thing
做错的事是做交易帮我当上律师
we did wrong was make a deal to get me into the Bar.
如果我通过听证会  帕默就动不了我们
If I pull out of that hearing, Palmer can't touch us.
你是...想想看你在说什么
Are you--think about what you're saying.
我不需要想
I don't need to think about it.
我不会丢下他们不管的
I'm not going to throw those guys under the bus.
-迈克  我们已经走到这一步  -我不管
- Mike, we've come too far - I don't care.
告诉赛德尔交易取消
Tell Seidel the deal's off.
如果还有别的办法呢
What if there was another way?
哈维  如果你是想另外找人
Harvey, if you're talking about somebody else
-来接这个案子  -不是
- handling this case - No, I'm not.
听着  赛德尔不可能是自己想到
Listen to me, there's no way Seidel came up with the idea
要卖情报给极速
to sell that shit to Velocity himself.
跟他出轨的女人肯定是为他们工作的
The woman he had an affair with has to work for them,
所以  我们可以拿她做筹码搞帕默
which means we can leverage her to sink Palmer.
-你开玩笑吗  -没有
- Are you kidding me? - No, I'm--
哈维  听听你自己  这可是不折不扣的
Harvey, listen to yourself. You're talking about out and out
敲诈和勒索
extortion and blackmail.
我不会为了成为律师
I'm not going to do any of that shit
做那样的事
just to get into the God damn Bar.
是你告诉我  你眼看那孩子输了官司
You were the one that told me that after watching that kid lose,
所以不想那种事再发生
you never wanted it to happen again.
现在那孩子告诉我们  这么做是错的
And now that same kid is telling us that what we're doing is wrong.
-他是对的  -迈克
- And he's right. - Mike.
不  哈维  够了
No, Harvey, it's enough.
你答应过瑞秋如果情况太危险
You promised Rachel that you'd pull the plug
就中止行动
if things got too risky.
现在
Well...
已经太危险了
it just got too God damn risky.
诉讼双雄 第六季 第十五集
怎么回事
What's going on?
天还未亮你就起床了
You got out of bed before it was light out.
还没回床上来
And you never came back.
我想跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you for a minute.
谈什么
About what?
我知道你去找哈维  逼他保证
I know you went to Harvey and you made him promise
如果我做律师的事太危险
to pull the plug on my getting into the Bar
就中止行动
if things got too risky.
他不该告诉你的
He wasn't supposed to tell you that.
你真觉得他不会说吗
Did you really think he wouldn't?
迈克  我让他对我那样承诺只是因为我在乎你
Mike, I only made him promise because I care about you.
没事  我知道原因
It's okay. I know why you did it.
也理解
And I understand it.
而且昨晚我自己已经叫停了这件事
And last night, I ended up pulling the plug myself.
-所以都结束了吗  -结束了
- So it's over? - It's over.
不当律师了
Not gonna be a lawyer.
迈克
Mike.
事实上  在哈维在我面前念叨这件事之前
The thing is, I was fine with it until Harvey started
我其实不太在意
dangling it in front of my face.
我觉得问题就出在我真的开始相信
I think the problem was, I actually started
这件事能成功了
believing it could happen.
你今天需要我陪你吗
Do you want me to stay with you today?
不用
No.
我没事
I'll be okay.
另外你今天有很多事要做
Besides, you've got a lot of work to do
我也有个大案子要赢
and I've got a big case to win.
哈维  你在这
Harvey, there you are.
路易要马上见你
Louis needs to see you right away.
唐娜  不论是什么事我现在都没时间
Donna, whatever it is, I don't have time right now.
那就挤时间出来
Well, you need to make time.
因为他昨晚就来找你了并且很沮丧
Because he came looking for you last night and he's upset.
对不起  唐娜  但我真的没时间听
Well, I'm sorry, Donna. But I'm too busy to hear about
他说和女朋友间的另一次危机
another crisis with his girlfriend
或者他的扑克俱乐部又怎么了
or drama in his canasta club
还是他的牙齿保护器不合适
or how his mouth guard doesn't fit.
时尚定制把我们解雇了
Couture Apparel fired us.
-什么  -卡莉很生气
- What? - Carly got upset that
路易没和你一起而带了瑞秋和卡特里娜参会
Louis brought Rachel and Katrina to the meeting instead of you.
他为她们辩解的时候  她就解雇了他
And when he stood up to her about it, she fired him.
混蛋
Shit.
哈维  他很内疚
Harvey, he feels terrible about it.
觉得自己让你失望了
He thinks he let you down.
他没有  是我让他失望了
Well, he didn't. I let him down.
而且到头来只是白忙一场
And it turns out it was all for nothing.
什么意思  什么叫白忙
What do you mean, nothing? What happened?
帕默猜到了赛德尔干的事
Palmer figured out what's going on with Seidel
迈克宁可拒绝他的条件也要继续这个案子
and Mike would rather pull his deal than drop the case.
那他就永远也当不了律师了
But then he'll never get into the Bar.
所以我才说我没时间
Why do you think I said I don't have time
处理任何别的事情
for anything else right now?
所以你是在说那个混蛋
So you're telling me that asshole's
完全控制了局面  迈克永远也当不了律师了
holding all the cards, and Mike's never gonna be a lawyer?
不  没有人能完全掌控局面
No, no one's ever holding all the cards.
我也不在乎迈克说什么
And I don't give a shit what Mike said,
我在知道能赢得情况下绝对不会弃牌
I'm not going folding when I know we can win.
路易  在你说话之前我想说
Louis, before you say anything,
唐娜已经告诉我了
Donna told me what happened.
-哈维  我很抱歉  -我知道
- Harvey, I am so sorry-- - I know you are.
但我来不是骂你的
But I didn't come here to scold you.
我来是因为我需要你的帮助
I came here because I need your help
否则迈克的协议就要告吹了
or Mike's deal is gonna fall apart.
为什么  怎么可能
What? How's that possible?
这么说吧  有人有控制我们的筹码
Let's just say someone's got leverage on us
我们也需要一点来对付他们
and I need to get leverage on them.
要什么筹码
What kind of leverage?
有个在极速公司工作的女人
There's a woman who works at Velocity.
她和赛德尔有私情
She had an affair with Seidel.
我需要知道她是谁
I need to know who she is.
极速公司有几千个员工
Thousands of people work at Velocity.
我知道  但能做到她做的事
Yeah, I know that. But to do what she did,
她肯定是个高层管理人员
she'd have to be a top corporate officer.
这确实能缩窄范围  但也需要
Well, that narrows it down. But it's still gonna require
大量的调查和几百个电话
huge amounts of research and hundreds of phone calls.
不  路易  只需要一个电话
No, Louis, it'll only require one phone call.
因为我需要的是接触到他们的数据库
Because what I need is access to their database.
不  哈维  总有别人可以做到的
No, Harvey, there's got to be someone else.
凡妮莎不做类似的事你也知道
Vanessa doesn't do this kind of thing and you know it.
我发过誓再也不和那个混蛋
I swore that I would never do business
有任何往来
with that son of a bitch again.
我知道  路易  但如果我们不做
I know that, Louis. But if we don't do this...
好吧  出去吧
All right, get out.
从外面把门关上
Close the door behind you.
-奥利佛  -怎么了
- Oliver. - What's up?
我们有事情做了
What's up is we got work to do.
迈克  我不想当混蛋
Mike, I don't mean to be an asshole,
但如果你不告诉纳森到底发生了什么的话
but I'm not doing anything until you tell Nathan
-我什么也不做了  -没什么好说的了
- exactly what's going on. - There's nothing to tell.
-你开玩笑吗  你说你接这个案子
- Are you kidding me? You said you were
是为了重新当律师
doing this case as a way to get into the Bar.
我刚刚撤回了我的申请
And I just withdrew my application.
没什么协议了  所以之前应当告诉纳森的事
There's no deal anymore. So whatever it was I was
也没必要再说了
gonna tell Nathan, I don't have to tell him anymore.
就这样  你放弃机会了
Just like that. You're giving up your chance?
听着  你昨晚说的那些话我听进去了
Look, I heard what you said to me last night
说要树立榜样
about setting an example.
所以与其告诉纳森
So instead of telling Nathan
我要做些见不得人的勾当
that I was up to something shady,
我是说我彻底不做了
I'm telling you that I'm not.
你需要我做什么
What do you need me to do?
我需要你去皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特
I need you to get down to PSL and grab half a dozen
抓几个律师来
of those associates and bring them back here.
你有什么打算
What are you gonna do?
我要竭尽所能确保这件事
I'm gonna do whatever I can to make sure
还没结束
this thing isn't over yet.
是的  让那些混蛋去死
Yeah, screw those assholes,
他们只是一些没种的废物
they're nothing but a bunch of dickless losers.
好的  我会为你把他们击垮
Yeah, I'll break them into little pieces for you,
我向你保证
you have my word on it.
好了  我要挂了  我也爱你  妈咪
All right, I got to go. I love you too, Mommy.
-斯图  -唐娜
- Stu. - Donna.
不得不说  我没想到你是个
Gotta say, I didn't figure you for a guy
会管母亲叫妈咪的人
who called his mother "Mommy."
我只能说  如果一个男人没有自信那么做
What can I say, if a man doesn't have the confidence to do that,
那他就不算个男人
then he's not really a man.
但我猜你大老远跑到这里来
But I'm guessing you didn't come all the way down here
绝不只是为了评价我和
just to evaluate my relationship
世界上最伟大的女人的关系的
with the greatest woman on Earth.
不  不是
No, I didn't.
我来是为了给你看这个
I came here to show you this.
-那是什么  -是个了不起的东西
- What's that? - It's a game-changer.
我在给你优先见证的机会
And I'm letting you in on the ground floor.
你这么说倒是很大胆
That's a bold statement.
打开吧
Turn it on.
你可以尽情享用
Keep it for as long as you want.
当你被震惊以后
And then when you're blown away,
就带着报价来找我吧
come back to me with an offer.
因为我和我的合伙人一定会大获成功
Because my partner and I, we're gonna go wide with this
我们需要一个投资人
and we're going to need an investor.
那你为什么来找我
Why are you coming to me with this?
因为我想给你个机会
Because I wanted to give someone the chance
将它推向市场
to take it off the market.
这个人一定要有自信
And it needed to be someone with the confidence
管母亲叫作妈咪
to call his mother "Mommy."
让我们来这见你真是你的风格
It's typical you would have us meet you here.
没用的人才来赌博
Gambling's for suckers, you know?
只有当结果是未知的时候才叫赌博
It's only gambling when the results are unknown.
局势对自己有利时  说好话没什么不对
There's nothing wrong with tilting the game in your favor.
我喜欢这家伙  路易
I like this guy, Louis.
为什么我之前没见过他
Why haven't I met him before?
你知道原因的  我们直入正题吧
You know why. So why don't we just get to it?
我们需要你黑进极速数据的员工记录
We need you to hack into Velocity Data's personnel records.
你能做到吗
Now, can you do it or not?
你要不要说得再大声点
You want to say that a little bit louder
让那边联调局的人听见
so the Fed over there can hear it?
放轻松  杰瑞  路易想表达的是
Relax, Jerry. What Louis is trying to say
有个在那里工作的女人
is there's a woman who works there
她手上有我们需要拿来做交易的信息
who has information we need to make a deal.
做交易
Make a deal?
我也说不好
Ah, I don't know.
我开始觉得这听上去像是勒索
That's starting to sound like blackmail,
这不在我的业务范围内啊
which is a little bit out of my league.
放屁  你就是干这个的
Bullshit. It's in your league.
我开始觉得你听上去像是在讨价还价了
And it's starting to sound like you're renegotiating,
你一向如此
like you always do.
你猜怎么着  路易
You know what, Louis?
这几年来我受够你的屁话了
I just about had enough of your bullshit over the years.
我讨价还价是因为你给我的报价低了
I renegotiate 'cause you low-ball me.
不  我告诉过...
No, I told--
杰瑞  这次你不是和路易做生意
Jerry, you're not dealing with Louis on this one,
而是和我
you're dealing with me.
你不如告诉我你要什么
So why don't you tell me what you need
然后我们把这事搞定
and let's get this thing done?
假如我需要黑进什么地方
If I'm gonna access anything,
你刚刚告诉我的那点信息可不够
I need to know more than you just told me.
因为假如我没拿到你想要的东西
'Cause I don't get what you want,
那也没有第二次机会了
there's no going back a second time.
好吧  有位极速的女员工
All right, there's a woman who works at Velocity
她和我客户公司的内部法律顾问睡在了一起
who slept with the in-house counsel at my client's company
然后说服他泄露了一些机密信息
and convinced him to sell confidential information.
我猜猜  她向他许诺
Let me guess, she promised him the Moon,
然后就把他晾在那儿了
then hung him out to dry.
没错  你为什么要知道
Yeah, why?
你不需要黑进极速的记录
You don't need to access Velocity's records.
-她不是他们的员工  -你怎么知道
- She doesn't work there. - How do you know?
因为我知道她是谁
Because I know who she is.
-我的报价要翻三倍  -三倍
- And the price just tripled. - Tripled?
你个虚伪的混蛋
You hypocritical piece of shit.
你都不用黑进哪里
You don't even have to access anything.
你知道那句老话是怎么说的
Well, you know what they say.
给管子工付钱不是因为他们敲了管子
You don't pay the plumber for banging on the pipes.
而是因为他们知道该往哪里敲
You pay him for knowing where to bang.
说得好
Yahtzee.
而且我告诉你  我敲的这个地方
And I'm telling you, where I'm banging,
可是会有很多东西掉出来的
a whole lot of shit's gonna fall out.
所以你们要么给足我钱  要么滚蛋
So you're either gonna pay up or you're not.
我打扰到你了吗
Am I interrupting?
和你说实话  我刚刚...
To tell you the truth, I've just been
盯着屏幕盯了15分钟了
staring at this screen for the past 15 minutes.
我每天做的就是这事  我称之为工作
That's what I do all day. I call it working.
但我猜你盯着屏幕不是为了工作吧
But I'm going to guess that's not why you're staring.
我是在想迈克
I was thinking about Mike.
他告诉你他放弃交易了
He told you he gave up the deal?
他说了  而且...
He did, and, um...
他还说他不当律师也没什么
he said that he's okay not being a lawyer.
但他的表情出卖了他
But the look on his face didn't say that at all.
那你可能会对我接下来要说的感兴趣
Then you might be interested in what I have to say.
因为这事最终让迈克能当上律师
Because it involves getting Mike into the Bar after all.
哈维  你为什么和我谈而不是和迈克谈
Harvey, why are you telling me this instead of Mike?
因为你说如果事情变得太危险
Because you asked me to pull the plug
我要及时叫停
on this whole thing if it got too risky,
而我所说的事
and what I'm talking about
会让整件事变得非常危险
is gonna make it a hell of a lot riskier.
那迈克是怎么说的
And what did Mike say?
-他不想这么做  -为什么
- He doesn't want to do it. - Why not?
你知道原因的  因为这并非完全合法
You know why not. It's not 100% legal.
假如你不想的话你也可以拒绝
And you can say no if you want to.
但你在他脸上看见的表情
But that look you saw on his face,
可就消失不了了
that's not going away any time soon.
好吧
Okay.
我加入
I'm in.
但这次如果出事了  你要来负责任
But this time, if something goes wrong, you take the fall.
好的  我会负责的
Okay, I will.
现在  你是打算继续盯着那块屏幕
Now, you gonna go back to staring at that thing
还是来帮我让迈克当上律师
or you want to help me get Mike into the Bar
同时找点乐子
and have some fun at the same time?
你需要我做什么
What do you need me to do?
我需要你回家去
I need you to go home,
换身好看很多的衣服
put on something a hell of a lot nicer,
然后一小时后和我在这个地址见
and meet me at this address in an hour.
宝贝
Hey, sweetie.
我马上就好
I'll be done in a few minutes.
-你今天过得怎样  -还好
- How's your day? - Fine.
路易  我们说过的
Louis, we talked about this.
你可以向我倾诉
You can share your day with me.
-我就是来逗你开心的  -不是那回事
- I'm here to cheer you up. - It's not that.
只是有时候
It's just that sometimes,
我不得不做一些不是那么好的事
I have to do some less than great things
和一些不是那么好的人合作
with less than great people
而我宁愿把这些记忆从我脑子里洗掉
and I'd rather wash the memories from my brain.
什么叫"不是那么好的事"
What do you mean, less than great things?
没什么  不是什么大事儿
Nothing, it's not that big a deal.
你是在说伤害一个无辜的人吗
Are you talking about hurting an innocent person?
不  当然不是
No, of course not.
那能有多糟糕
Then how bad can it be?
完全没有那么糟糕  塔拉
Well, it's not that bad at all, Tara.
实际上  我所做的一切
As a matter of fact, I'm doing it all
都是为了帮助某个我很关心的人
to help someone I care deeply about.
而有时为了做好事
And sometimes to do good,
免不了会用一些不太干净的手段
you gotta get a little dirty.
也许你可以带我回家
Well, then maybe you can take me home
对我用一些不太干净的手段
and get a little dirty with me.
亲爱的  我想啊
Oh, sweetie, I want to
但我现在不太有心情
but I'm just not in the mood.
你确定不想向我倾诉一下吗
Are you sure this isn't something you wanna share with me?
-我确定  -好吧
- Yes, I'm sure. - Okay.
当我希望你知道
But I want you to know,
无论什么事你都可以和我说的
you can tell me anything.
塔拉  抱歉  但我不能和你一块回家了
Tara, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to meet you at home.
怎么了
Oh, what is it?
没什么  我只是得去见哈维一面  好吗
Nothing, I just have to go see Harvey, okay?
好的
Okay.
路易  我只有两分钟
Louis, I've got about two minutes.
我和瑞秋约了
I'm gonna meet Rachel.
那就花两分钟看看这个
Well, take two minutes to look at this.
-这是什么  -艾伦・菲尔兹的来信
- What is it? - It's a letter from Allen Fields.
该死
Shit.
因为我们近期的人员变动
He's putting us in review
他要重新考虑是否继续用我们
based on our recent affiliations.
你知道那是什么意思吧
You know what that means.
我当然知道
Yeah, I sure as hell do.
那你应该知道我刚刚收到另外十封信
Well, then you should know that I just got ten more
是另外十个客户发来的
from ten other clients
他们都是这个意思
and they all say the same thing.
那个混蛋
That son of a bitch.
路易  我不会被威胁的
Louis, I'm not gonna be bullied.
不  我不在乎你要怎么做
No, I don't care what you're gonna be.
现在  我们丢掉了时尚定制公司
Now, we lost Couture Apparel
因为你忙着处理迈克的事
because you were too busy with Mike.
现在这情况完全一致
This is the same exact thing in different clothes.
-路易  -哈维
- Louis. - Harvey,
我刚刚得向我爱的女人撒谎
I just had to lie to the woman I love
因为我不想说出关于迈克的真相
because I didn't want to admit the whole truth about Mike.
现在  我愿意孤注一掷利用杰瑞
Now, I'm willing to go with the Hail Mary of using Jerry.
但我不愿意拿我们律所冒险
But what I am not willing to do is risk our survival.
-路易  -哈维  够了
- Louis. - Harvey, that is enough.
你知道需要做什么
You know what needs to be done.
解决它  否则我会做的
Do it, or I will.
帕默先生
Mr. Palmer.
我想你并没有看到备忘录
I take it you didn't get the memo.
这个案子已经结束了
This case is over.
那是因为还没有结束
Well, that's because it's not.
这是什么
What the hell is this?
那是我写给纽约律师协会的信的副本
That's a copy of my letter to the New York Bar,
我要把自己从备选名单上除名
removing myself from consideration.
没有面试  没有申请
No interview, no application,
没有交换条件
no quid pro quo,
也就是说这案子远远没有结束
which means this case is far from over.
你一定是在开玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
我要放弃成为律师的机会
You're gonna give up your chance to be a lawyer
就为了在上周之前你甚至都不认识的矿工
for some miners you didn't even know existed before last week?
我现在认识了
Well, I know they exist now.
我还知道因为你  他们就要死了
And I know they're dying because of you.
所以  我们不仅要解决这件事
So, we're gonna settle this thing
而且现在就要解决
and we're going to settle it right now.
我来告诉你我会怎么做
Well, I'll tell you what I'll do.
我会写给你一张1000万的支票
I'll write you a check for ten million right here.
1000万
Ten million?
你他妈在说什么
The hell are you talking about?
你告诉他们是一个亿了  是不是
Oh, you told them you'd get them a hundred, didn't you?
是的  我可以从你的脸上看出来
Yeah, you did. I can see it in your face.
我建议你告诉他们你不小心多加了个0
Well, I suggest you tell them you accidentally added a zero.
因为除此之外  你不会再拿到一分钱
Because you're not getting a nickel more.
让我提醒你一下  帕默先生
Let me remind you, Mr. Palmer.
我们对你提出了150件诉讼
We filed 150 suits against you.
我们每一场官司都会打
And we are gonna fight them all.
那之前对我是个震慑
And that shook me before.
但是谁现在会提供人力去打那些官司呢
But who's gonna supply the manpower to fight those suits now?
你知道的
You know who.
我看你是真的没有收到备忘啊
I guess you really didn't get the memo, did you?
因为皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特
Because Pearson Specter Litt
刚刚撤出了这个案子
just withdrew from this case.
我会找到其他人的
I'll find someone else.
我很怀疑
I highly doubt it.
听着
Hey, listen to me.
你的公司伤害了这些人
Your company hurt these people.
你之前愿意以1亿的价格和解
You were willing to settle for a hundred million before.
这是你可以做正确的选择
This is your chance to do the right thing
同时还可以让你无愧于你的良知的机会
and clear your conscience at the same time.
听起来像是让你无愧于心的机会
Sounds to me like a chance to clear yours.
要么接受这个提议  要么放弃  罗斯先生
This is a take-it-or-leave-it offer, Mr. Ross.
不管你接受与否
And whether you take it or not,
我都不想再在这见到你
I don't ever expect to see you here again.
-科伦维尔小姐  -怎么
- Ms. Cromwell?  - Yes.
我是米歇尔・罗斯
My name's Michelle Ross
我想雇你做事
and I was hoping to employ your services.
我的服务
My services?
我是兰-考-赞律所的初级合伙人
Yes, I'm a junior partner at Rand Kaldor,
我正找机会想做出改变
and I'm looking to make a change.
抱歉  我不怎么和法律部门一起工作
I'm sorry, I don't really do much work with the legal sector.
事实上  我想把我的经验
Actually, I was hoping to use my experience
用到商业世界中
and parlay it into the business world.
我可以收下你的简历  但说实话
Well, I can take your résumé, but to be honest,
我并没有客户在找
I don't have a client who's looking for a candidate
-像你一样的候选人  -我知道没有
- like you at the moment. - I know you don't.
事实上  既然我们都实话实说了
In fact, since we're being honest,
你知道你要找什么样的候选人
I know exactly what kind of candidate you're looking for.
什么样的
What kind is that?
可以被操控
One that can be manipulated
出卖他们雇主产品的人
into selling their employer's products.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who I am.
重要的是我知道你做了什么
What matters is I know what you do.
你一点都不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我知道你明面上是个猎头
I know that you're officially a headhunter,
但是背地里  你在这样的地方
but unofficially, you meet your exclusively male clients
见你的高级男性客户
at places like this.
我还知道在这些会面的结尾
I also know that at the end of each of those meetings,
你会和他们说  "我从未这样做过
you say to them, "I never do this,
"但是你想一起吃晚餐吗"
"but would you like to have dinner?"
晚餐之后是甜点
And then dinner leads to dessert,
甜点之后就上床
dessert leads to sex,
上床之后则让他们喜欢上你
and sex leads to them falling for you,
-然后  -好了  够了
- and that leads to-- - All right, I've heard enough.
你没有任何证据
And you don't have proof of anything.
事实上  我有
Actually, I do.
但你知道吗  我并不需要
But you know what? I don't need it.
因为只可能有两种情况
Because one of two things is going to happen.
一种是我雇人告诉你的每一位
Either I'm going to hire someone to tell every one
男性客户  当你和他们见面的时候
of your male clients when they meet them
你准备抢劫他们
that you're going to rob them,
然后你每单可以轻轻松松的
and then your cushy job making a million dollars per sucker
-挣100万美元  -又或者
- is going away- - Or?
又或者你告诉我
Or you're gonna tell me
你每次帮詹姆斯・帕默这么做的情况
about every time you've done this for James Palmer,
你就再也不会见到我俩了
and you're never gonna hear from either one of us again.
我不能那样做
I can't do that.
我的工作要求要有个慎重的好名声
My job requires a reputation for discretion.
你按我们说的做
You're gonna do what we want,
否则你就会知道
or you're gonna find out
你的好名声在监狱中能护你几分
how much your reputation protects you in prison.
我懂了  你不担心帕默知道这件事
Oh, I get it. You're not worried about Palmer knowing.
你担心的是消息会传播出去
You're worried about word spreading.
相信我  他不会告诉任何人的
Trust me, he'll never tell a soul
你的生意也不会受到影响
and your business will stay intact.
你怎么能这样肯定
How can you be sure?
和我确定你没有别的选择一样
The same way I'm sure that you don't have a choice.
问题是  你准备和他作对
The question is, are you gonna go against him
还是和我作对
or are you gonna go against me?
好  我加入
Okay, I'm in.
-就这样  -就这样
- Just like that? - Just like that.
这东西真他妈令人印象深刻
This thing is damn impressive.
但是在我们进行下一步之前
But before we move forward,
我得确定你和我能在一件事上达成共识
I need to make sure you're good with one thing.
什么
What's that?
我要百分之九十的股权
I want 90% ownership.
百分之九十  你疯了吗
90%? Are you out of your mind?
并没有
No, I'm not.
我不做风险投资
And I'm not in the venture capital business.
我做的是股票市场投资
I invest in the stock market.
这意味着我得用自己的钱
Which means I'd be using my own money on this.
这钱你肯定能挣回来
Money that you'd earn back in spades.
我希望是这样
I hope it turns out that way,
但这些事风险很大
but this thing has a lot of risk,
而且我要承担全部风险
and I'd be taking all of it.
那也许你不应该承担任何风险
Then maybe you should take none of it.
唐娜  这东西虽然好
Donna, as good as this product is,
以商人对商人的谈话  我明说吧
I'm telling you--as one business person to another--
你做生意还没有积累到信誉
you have no credibility to do this.
相信我  这是你能得到的最好条件了
Believe me, these are the best terms you're gonna get.
你看  这你就错了  斯图
Well...you see, that's where you're wrong, Stu.
因为正如我曾告诉过你的
Because like I told you once before,
我是唐娜
I'm Donna,
这很棒
this is awesome,
而我能做得更好
and I can do better.
我希望你能证明我是错的
Well, I hope you prove me wrong.
但同时  我不想让你做找马时骑的驴
But in the meantime, I won't be used as a stalking horse.
这意味着如果你现在走了
Which means if you walk away now,
你以后就别回来找我了
you can't come back to me later.
你不必担心  斯图
Oh, you don't have to worry about that, Stu.
因为我一旦走出那扇门
Because once I walk out that door,
我保证不会再回来了
I promise you I'm not coming back.
真不敢相信
I can't believe you.
听着  迈克  在你开口前
Listen, Mike, before you say anything--
我知道你根本不在乎那些矿工
I know you didn't give a shit about those miners,
但你至少可以
but the least you could've done
坚持一下  给我一点筹码
is stuck around long enough to give me some leverage.
我们别无选择
We had no choice.
帕默给我们的十个顶级客户施压
Palmer pressured ten of our top clients
让他们解雇我们  除非我们放弃
to drop us unless we pulled out.
所以就是选他们还是选我了
So it's either them or me?
除非你能代替他们的三千万账单
Unless you can replace 30 million in billings,
那就是这样
you're damn right it is.
哈维  如果你不帮我
Harvey, without you backing me,
那些矿工就完了
those miners are screwed.
而且我只能束手无策
And there is nothing that I can do about it.
你可以对此有所作为
There's something you can do about it,
你只是不愿意做
you just don't wanna do it.
你说的是那个女人
You're talking about that woman.
你想对帕默施加影响吗
You want leverage on Palmer?
她就是能影响帕默的人
She's the one who's got it.
哈维  我们说过了
Harvey, we've been over this.
我不打算利用那个女人
I'm not gonna use that woman.
如果我告诉你我们已经这样做了呢
And what if I told you we already did?
-什么  -迈克  我们不仅找到了她
- What? - Mike, we not only found her,
还拿到了足以让那混蛋和解的料
we got enough to force that bastard into a settlement.
问题在于  你是否愿意利用它
The question is: are you willing to use it?
你说"我们"是什么意思
What do you mean "We"?
-迈克  -不  你刚刚说了"我们"
- Mike. - No, no, you just said, "We."
"我们"是指谁
Who the hell is "We"?
瑞秋
Rachel.
我和瑞秋
Me and Rachel.
你把瑞秋卷进这件事了
You dragged Rachel into this.
我没有把她卷进任何事
I didn't drag her into anything.
我去征求她的同意  因为我明白你的感受
I went to her for permission because I knew how you felt,
她立刻抓住了这个你因为太蠢而不愿抓的机会
and she jumped at the chance since you're too stupid to.
你没权利这样做
You had no right.
-迈克  听着  -你没有权利
- Mike, listen. - You had no right!
晚安  强尼
Good night, Johnny.
本杰明
Benjamin?
唐娜
Donna.
希望我来你住处找你你不会觉得很奇怪
I hope you don't think it's weird that I came to your place.
你知道我的住处  这让我有点奇怪
Well, I find it a little weird that you know where I live.
我在信息技术部门工作  知道所有人的住处
I work in IT. I know where everyone lives.
但我来这里不是要说这些的
But that's not what I came here to talk about.
你来这里做什么
What did you come here for?
我非常担心明天
I'm freaking out about tomorrow
如果我们还没准备好怎么办
and what if we're not ready?
放松  本杰明  会好的
Relax, Benjamin. It's gonna be fine.
你怎么知道
How can you know that?
因为我已经演练过了
Because I already did a practice run.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我知道有个人可能会投资
There's a guy I know who I thought might invest,
但他并不是做这行的
but he's not really in this business
我带着真・唐娜去找他  游说了一番
so I brought the Donna over to him and I gave him our pitch.
进展顺利吗
And it went okay?
不只是顺利  他给我们报价了
It went more than okay. He made us an offer.
那我们究竟为什么
Then what in God's name do we need
还要这么折磨自己
to put ourselves through this torture for?
我拒绝了他
I turned him down.
等等  什么
Wait -- what?
唐娜  这是我们的梦想
Donna, this is our dream.
我知道  本杰明
I know that, Benjamin.
但他想要90%的所有权
But wanted to own 90% of it,
而我不想放弃我们90%的梦想
and I'm not willing to give up 90% of our dream.
现在回家睡个觉
Now go home and get some sleep,
因为我们明天是我们的第一次展示会
because we've got our first meeting tomorrow
咱们会大获成功的
and you and I are gonna kick some serious ass.
-你打算什么时候告诉我  -迈克
- When were you gonna tell me? - Mike--
你想过要告诉我吗
Were you ever gonna God damn tell me?
别这样跟我说话
Don't speak to me like that.
你明知我的态度  却还背着我做这些
You went behind my back when you knew how I felt about this.
不  我背着你做这些
No, I went behind your back
正是因为我明白你的感受
because I knew how you felt about it.
这样就能把你的行为正当化了吗
Is that supposed to make it okay?
不  听着  我才是那个
No, look, I was the one
不希望冒太大风险的人
that didn't want to let things get too risky,
但是当哈维跟我说过之后
but when Harvey laid it out for me,
我认为这并不是冒险
I decided that it wasn't.
那你为什么不先来找我
Then why didn't you come to me first?
因为你说过
Because you're the one that says
要求原谅比要求许可更容易
forgiveness is easier to ask for than permission.
这个理由太烂了
That's a bullshit reason.
那你怎么不想想  我是为了你才这么做的
Then how about focusing on the fact that I did it for you?
-瑞秋  -迈克  今天早上
- Rachel - Mike, this morning,
当你告诉我已经结束了
when you told me it was over,
你的表情...
the look on your face--
我不希望你的余生都是这样的表情
I don't want you to have that look for the rest of your life.
瑞秋  我那时很沮丧  事情刚刚发生
Rachel, I was upset. It had just happened.
不  迈克  问题就是  它不是刚发生
No, Mike, that's just it. It hadn't.
你背负这些太久了
You've been living with this for so long,
这就是为什么你允许哈维去做这件事
that's why you gave Harvey the go-ahead to begin with.
我那么做是因为我要看着奥利佛失败
I did that because I had to watch Oliver fail
而我无计可施
and there's nothing I could do about it.
如果不是奥利佛
And if it wasn't Oliver,
就会有其他的人
it was going to be someone else.
或者其他的事
Or something else.
总会有什么来提醒你  你不是律师
There's always gonna be some reminder that you weren't a lawyer.
它会逐渐吞噬你
And it would eat away at you,
因为你命中注定要成为律师
because it's what you're meant to be.
你不应该做你做的那些事
You shouldn't have done what you did.
我知道  我背着你做这些你很生气
I know you're mad at me for going behind your back,
但我不会道歉的
but I'm not gonna apologize.
因为我不愿意和一个放弃了梦想的人
Because I don't wanna spend the rest of my life with a man
过一辈子
who gave up on his dreams.
而且我知道你也不愿意当那个人
And I know that you don't wanna be that man either.
路易
Louis?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing in here?
瑞秋  我能跟你谈谈吗
Rachel, can I talk to you a second?
当然
Of course.
我听说迈克不希望卷入那个女人
I heard Mike had a problem involving that woman.
是的
Yes, he did.
我们昨晚其实还为这事吵了架
We actually got into a fight about it last night.
-他什么打算  -我不知道
- What's he gonna do? - I don't know.
但还是要感谢你为了找她做的一切
But thank you for doing whatever you did to find her, anyway.
没事
Of course.
所以  你来找我什么事
So... what are you doing in here?
你有希望你从来没发现过吗
You ever wish you hadn't found out?
-什么  -你有希望过
- What? - You ever wish
你从来没发现迈克的秘密吗
you never known about Mike's secret?
或者再远点  从来没遇到过他
Or, for that matter, never even met him?
路易  到底怎么了
Louis, what's going on?
塔拉和我最近一直在交流生活
Tara and I have been sharing a lot lately.
但我还是有没告诉她的事
But there's still things I haven't told her.
昨天  她问我我为什么心情不好
Yesterday, she asked me what I was having a bad day about.
而事实是  就是因为迈克的事
And the truth is, it was pretty much about Mike.
而且我想告诉她  但是...
And I want to tell her about it, but--
你不知道她会作何反应
You don't know how she'll react.
是的  我甚至都不敢告诉她
No, I don't. I still haven't even told her
在迈克事发前我就知道他的秘密
I knew about Mike's secret before he got caught,
更别说我还利用他的秘密当了冠名合伙人
let alone the fact that I used it to get made partner.
-路易  -瑞秋  当时被希拉发现时
- Louis... - Rachel, when Sheila found out,
她说我再也不是她的灵魂伴侣了
she said I wasn't her soul mate anymore.
但那是希拉  路易
But that was Sheila, Louis.
而且关键字是  被她发现
And the key phrase is "She found out."
不是你主动告诉她的
You didn't tell her.
所以迈克告诉你的时候你就不生气吗
So you were okay when Mike told you?
不  我不能说我完全没有生气
No, I wouldn't say that I was okay with it.
但我爱他
But I love him.
所以我原谅了他
That's why I forgave him.
我不能保证塔拉会原谅你
I can't guarantee that Tara will forgive you,
但我肯定如果哪天被她自己发现了
but I can tell you that if she finds out some other way,
那她肯定不会原谅你了
then she won't.
谢谢  瑞秋
Thank you, Rachel.
谢谢你能陪我谈谈这件事
I appreciate your time.
谢谢答应和我们见面
Thank you for sitting down with us.
很荣幸  我是安德鲁  这是拉塞尔
It's our pleasure. I'm Andrew and this is Russell.
-我是唐娜  -我叫本杰明
- I'm Donna. - And my name is Benjamin.
介意我叫你本吗
Mind if I call you Ben?
说实话  非常介意
Yes, actually, I mind very much.
但只要你打开支票本签了我们
But you open up that checkbook of yours,
你想怎么叫本都可以
and you can call Ben here whatever the hell you want.
谢谢  但开始前
I appreciate that, but before we get started,
你要知道  我们一个月
you should know that we get pitched
能得到六个个人助手设备的提案
six personal assistant devices a month.
你也要知道我们的设备
And you should know that our device
能让Siri和Alexa黯然失色
makes Siri and the Alexa look like toaster ovens.
也许如此
Well, that may be the case,
但我担心市场已经饱和了
but I'm concerned that the market is already saturated.
你要真担心
If you were so concerned,
那就不会接受这次面谈了
you wouldn't be sitting here in the first place.
-是吗  -是的
- Is that a fact? - Yes, it is.
因为你是投资部的老大
Because you're the head of the investment team,
老大是不会随便浪费时间的
and the head of the team doesn't waste his time
除非他觉得有利可图
unless he thinks there might be something in it for him.
我图的利也不一定就非是投资
There might be other things in it for me than just investing.
确实
Yes, there could.
权利斗争就有可能
Like marking your territory.
因为看到你们俩坐在这儿谁都能看出
Because anybody can see by the way you two are sitting there
他想夺你的位子  而且你对此非常不爽
that he's gunning for your job and you don't like that one bit.
-不是的...  -谁告诉你的
- That's not-- - Who told you that?
没人告诉我
No one told me that.
就像也没人告诉我你不能解雇他
Just like no one told me that you can't fire him
因为这会显得你很软弱一样
because that'll make you look weak.
所以你才接受了这次面谈
Which is why you took this meeting.
因为你不愿意他单独来见我们
Because you didn't want him taking it without you.
好吧  你到底是怎么做到的
Okay, how in the hell are you doing all this?
我能做到因为我是唐娜
I'm doing this because I'm Donna.
如果你们还没明白  这个设备也是唐娜
And if it hasn't dawned on you already, so is this device.
所以  你们是想继续鼓着劲搞办公室政治
Now, do you wanna puff up your chest and play office politics,
还是想听一个能让你们
or do you wanna hear about an opportunity
都步步高升的好机会
that could vault you both to the top of the ladder?
不如请你给我们介绍一下你的产品
Why don't you tell us about your product?
请给我一杯黑咖啡
Can I get a black coffee?
他要的来两份
Make it two of whatever he's having.
你又来骂我背着你
You here to tell me what a dick I am
行动的事太混蛋了吗
for going behind your back again?
不是  我来问你什么时候去见帕默
No, I'm here to find out what time your meeting with Palmer is.
不知道
I don't know.
什么叫你不知道
What do you mean, you don't know?
因为没有你的允许我不打算行动
Well, I wasn't gonna do it without your permission.
所以就是说我没跟帕默约时间呢
Which means there is no meeting with Palmer.
那我现在允许了
Well, I'm giving you my permission.
迈克  不是我抱怨
Mike, I'm not trying to be an asshole,
但我们费了好大的功夫才拿到帕默的把柄
but we went to a lot of trouble to get that shit on Palmer
结果你一副想杀我的样子
and you looked like you wanted to kill me.
我怎么知道这次你就不会后悔了
So how do I know you're not gonna wanna change your mind?
因为我想当律师
'Cause I wanna be a lawyer.
我不在乎用什么方法办到
I don't care how we do it.
钱包拿出来  把我的帐付了
Take out your wallet, pay for this coffee,
然后我们一起拿下这件事
and let's bring this thing home.
那是我这辈子最非凡的27分钟
Well, that was the most amazing 27 minutes of my entire life.
哪部分非凡啊
Which part?
是你坐在那一句话也说不出来
When you sat there with your mouth glued shut
还是讲到运行系统掉链子的时候
or when you shit the bed describing the operating system?
天  就知道说到设计规格的时候就该闭嘴了
Oh, my God, I knew I should have stopped after the design specs.
本杰明  我逗你玩的
Benjamin, I'm teasing you.
我真的不知道这句话可信不可信
Now I don't know if I should believe you.
那你听好了
Then listen to me carefully.
你棒极了
You killed it.
谢谢  但是  其实是我们棒极了
Thank you. But, in fact, we killed it.
一点没错  是我们
You're damn right, we did.
你先走吧  我们回公司再见
Now get going, I'm gonna see you back at the firm.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我不小心把笔忘在会议室了
I accidentally forgot my pen in the conference room.
我可以借你一支
Oh, I have one you can borrow.
本杰明  当我说不小心时
Benjamin, when I say accidentally,
我的意思是我故意忘在了那里
I mean intentionally
好找个借口回去在门口偷听
because it gives me an excuse to go back in there
他们是怎么谈论我们的
and eavesdrop on what they're saying about us.
好主意  让我一起去吧
Oh, that's a great idea. Can I come with you?
-不  我得一个人去  -为什么
- No, I need to do this alone. - Why?
因为当他们看到只有我回去时
Because when they see me without you,
会觉得他们二对一占优势
they're gonna think it's two against one
所以会向我提议甩掉你单干
and they'll make me an offer to cut you out.
等等  你真觉得他们会那么做
Wait, you actually think they would do that?
当然  这些家伙可是腐肉都不放过的秃鹫
Of course they will. These guys are vultures.
那我不该跟你一起回去  阻止他们吗
Well, then shouldn't I go with you so we can stop it?
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
当然
Yes, I do.
那就相信我  他们会给我开价
Then trust when they make me the offer,
我会表现出愤怒的样子
I'm gonna act outraged,
告诉他们我们绝不跟他们合作
tell them we'll never do business with them,
他们就会给我们再加百分之五
and they'll give us an extra 5% right there.
-你觉得呢  -我觉得很惊人
- So what'd you think? - I thought it was impressive.
那你们也太容易惊讶了
Oh, then I think you're easily impressed.
-你不喜欢吗  -我还行
- You didn't like it? - I liked it just fine.
但你知道推出一款这样的技术
But do you know how much it costs to roll out
要花多少钱吗
a piece of tech like that?
从工程设计到试用机
Between the engineering design, and beta testing.
要花太多钱
It costs a ton of money.
是你说要先花钱才能赚钱的
Hey, you're the one who says you gotta spend money to make money.
我还说过投项目就是投人
I also said when you fund a project, you fund the person.
所以相信我  我不会投资那个女人
And the truth is, I'm not funding that woman.
那我们为什么还要见他们
So, why'd we take this meeting?
给哈维・斯佩克特送人情
Took it as a favor to Harvey Specter.
如果她要开柠檬水站
Now, if she was starting up a lemonade stand,
我可能会投点钱进去
I might throw in a few bucks.
但我绝对不可能跟一个律师秘书
But there is no way in hell I'm getting into business
一起创业
with a career legal secretary.
理解了
You don't have to tell me twice.
-要去吃饭吗  -喝一杯也行
- You wanna grab some lunch? - Yeah, and maybe a drink.
我绷着脸坐了这么久
I feel like I deserve it after having to
也应该来一杯犒劳一下自己
sit through that with a straight face.
詹姆  俱乐部选得不错
Hey, Jimbo, nice club.
但在我看来木器太多了
A little heavy on the wood for my taste.
对我来说是蠢货有点多
A little heavy on the douche bag for mine.
你怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
我跟他们说我是你表弟
I told them I was your cousin.
有点坏消息  你需要知道
We had some bad news and you were gonna wanna hear about it.
-胡说  -表弟那部分是胡说
- Bullshit. - Maybe not the cousin part,
但消息是这样的
but here's the news:
我们抓到了你的把柄
we got your balls in a vice.
-只有一个解决办法  -是呀
- There's only one way out. - The hell you do.
既然你决定跑回这里了
And since you decided to just wade back into this,
你那六个客户就没了
those six clients of yours are gone.
我不这么想  瘦子吉姆
Mm. Don't think so, Slim Jim.
你看  你第一次差点难住我们
See, the only reason you almost got to us in the first place
是因为你发现了我的阿基里斯之踵
was you found my Achilles Heel.
但我们现在发现了你的
But then we found yours.
我得说  她确实很漂亮
I gotta say, she sure is pretty.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
这个说不定能提醒你
Maybe this'll jog your memory.
姓名  日期  电话  邮件
Names, dates, phone numbers, emails,
银行账户  金钱往来
bank statements, wire transfers.
能证明超过一打的
Proof of over a dozen instances
商业间谍行为
of you committing corporate espionage.
我们的幸运之处在于  她不仅漂亮
Lucky for us, she isn't just pretty,
还喜欢什么都记下来
she's a hell of a bookkeeper.
你们想要什么
What do you want?
要你一开始就该做的事
For you to do what you should have done in the first place.
跟那些矿工以两亿美金和解
You're gonna settle with those miners for 200 million.
你忘记听说过我们或者科伦维尔女士的事
You're gonna forget you ever heard of us or Ms. Cromwell.
并且继续诚实履行跟克雷格・塞德尔
And you're gonna honor your original agreement
原本达成的协议
with Craig Seidel.
你干嘛要关心那只黄鼠狼的将来
What do you care about that weasel's future for?
这是我跟他的事
That's between me and him.
还有件事
Oh, one other thing.
这才是个真的过这个村没这个店的交易
This really is a take-it-or-leave-it offer.
15秒后失效
Expires in 15 seconds.
等你签了
And once it's signed,
我永远不想听到你的破公司
I never wanna hear about your shitty little company
再做这样的事情
doing something like this ever again.
好了
There you are.
那个会后你去哪了
Where have you been since that meeting?
我一直在想一些事
I've been doing some thinking.
而我整天都在担心我的合伙人是不是出卖了我
And I've been wondering if my partner sold me out all day.
本杰明  我不想告诉你
Well...I hate to break it to you, Benjamin,
但事实完全相反
but that's actually the opposite of what happened.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他们不想提合作
I mean...they don't want to make us an offer.
事实上  他们不想跟真・唐娜有任何关系
In fact, they don't want anything to do with The Donna.
-是我的错  对吗  -本杰明
- It's my fault, isn't it? - Benjamin--
你不必保护我的感情
You don't have to protect my feelings.
链条的强度要看最薄弱的一环
A chain is only as strong as its weakest link,
我知道那就是我
and I know that's what I am.
不  不是你
No, you're not.
事实上是我
It turns out I am.
听我说
Listen to me.
你制造了不可思议的产品
You have designed an incredible product.
我不想拖你的后退
And I don't want to hold you back.
所以  现在我要解散我们的合伙关系
Which is why, as of right now, I am dissolving our partnership
好让你一个人发布它
so you can take it out on your own.
你这是要去哪
Where the hell do you think you're going?
我们是合伙人  没有你
We're partners--I'd rather throw
我宁愿把真・唐娜丢进海里
The Donna into the ocean than move forward without you.
本杰明  拜托
Benjamin, please.
别做牺牲者
Don't be a martyr.
我不是在做牺牲者
I'm not being a martyr.
我是在做合伙人
I'm being a partner.
我们要一起做  要不就都退出
We're in this together or not at all.
所以就只看你了
So it's up to you.
我们是要放弃梦想
Are we gonna give up on our dream
还是继续为它奋斗
or live to fight another day?
继续奋斗  本杰明
Live to fight, Benjamin.
继续奋斗
Live to fight.
你又来
Again?
这次又是什么鬼事
What the hell is it this time?
跟上次一样的事
Same thing as it was last time.
我需要你帮我争取听证会
I need you to get that hearing back for me.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你知道第一次惹了多少麻烦吗
You know how much trouble it was the first time?
我不关心有多少麻烦
I don't care how much trouble it was.
你得再做一次
You're gonna do it again.
当然  除非你不想要
Unless, of course, you don't want the original terms
你跟帕默原来的协议了
of your deal with Palmer upheld.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们让他保证了付你原本承诺的金额
We had him guarantee to pay you what he promised
并在本季度结束后雇佣你
and to hire you over there at the end of the quarter.
你们为什么这么做
Why would you do that?
因为我不仅想让你敲定听证
'Cause I don't just want you to set that hearing,
我想让你帮我清除掉所有拦路的人
I want you to bulldoze anyone who stands in my way.
选择权在你
Look, it's up to you.
你拿钱和工作  让我进去
You take the job and the money and you get me in
或者坐在要沉的船上  等他们
or you stay on a sinking ship and wait for them to figure out
发现你就是弄沉它的人
that you're the one who sank it.
我会做到
I'll make it happen.
没错  我也觉得
Yeah, I'm not surprised.
我以为你现在正在找乐子呢
I would've thought you'd be at happy hour by now.
这些天我的乐子只在
These days my happy hour is the 60 minutes
从我回家到昏睡过去之间的60分钟
from the time I get home to the time I pass out.
你真是工作狂  斯图
You're a hard worker, Stu.
事实是世界不会为看脸付钱
Turns out they don't just give you money for your looks.
但你肯定不是跑这么远来告诉我
But you didn't come all the way back here
我有多努力的
just to tell me how hard I work.
我来看看你愿不愿意重新考虑
I came to see if you'd reconsider.
你没能搞定  是吗
You couldn't beat it, could you?
是  但我不是因为这才来
No. But that's not why I'm here.
那是为什么
Then why are you here?
因为虽然我不喜欢你的条件
Because even though I didn't like your terms,
但你平等对待我  尊重我
you spoke to me as an equal and you treated me with respect
而我想跟这样的人合作做生意
and that's the kind of person I want to be in business with.
如果我说
What would you say
我的提议还在呢
if I told you the offer was back on the table?
我会说我猜条件
I'd say my assumption is the terms won't be
不会像上次一样好了
as good as they were the first time around.
条件不变
The terms aren't gonna change.
为什么
Why not?
因为我不想让和我合伙做生意的人
Because I don't want to go into business with someone
觉得我就是为了坑他们
who feels like I'm giving them the shaft.
我乐意跟喜欢我
I wanna go into business with someone
做合伙人的人合作
who's happywith my partnership.
谢谢  斯图
Thank you, Stu.
不客气  唐娜
You're welcome, Donna.
而且跟你说
Oh, and just so you know,
我说要付诸行动
when I put my money where my mouth is,
就会投入一切
I throw everything I have into it.
那既然你敢说这么大的话
I wouldn't expect anything less
我也就不担心了
from a big mouth like you.
搞定了
Done?
Done.
我得说
I gotta say,
有你做律师  世界会好一点
the world's gonna be a better place with you as a lawyer.
为什么  因为我们强迫了某些混蛋
Why? 'Cause we just strong-armed some jackass
做了我们想要的事吗
into doing what what we want?
不  因为你不惜一切代价
No, because you did what it took
给那些矿工争取了他们应得的
to get those miners what they deserve.
说到这个  你喝完酒想跟我来吗
Speaking of which, you wanna come with me after this?
-去哪  -去告诉那些矿工
- Where you going? - To tell those miners
世上最好的律师  帮他们争取到了应得的
that the world's best lawyer just got them what they deserve.
-是第二好  -没什么区别
- Second best. - Ah, potato/potahto.
说真的  迈克  还是你去吧
Seriously, Mike, you go tell them.
另外  说完之后
Besides, after that,
你得为听证会做准备了
you've got some preparing to do for that hearing.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我已经说了  塞德尔搞定这事了
I just told you, Seidel's got it in the bag.
你要觉得这事不会出问题
And if you think there isn't gonna be some kind of hitch,
-那我真什么都没教会你  -如果你觉得
- I haven't taught you shit. - If you think whatever it is,
我没法处理要出的事  那就是没注意我
I can't handle it, then you have not been paying attention.
你是说你把自己处理进监狱的事吗
You mean like when you handled yourself into going to prison?
不  我是说我一身玫瑰香出来
No, I mean when I came out smelling like a rose.
你出来的时候我在
Hey, I was there when you came out.
你那个味道肯定不是玫瑰香
And rose wasn't the aroma you were emanating.
没错
You're right.
我那个味道是完美
I was emanating awesome.
你真是很像我啊  对吧
You really are like me, aren't you?
真不幸  是的
Unfortunately.
欢迎回到律师圈  迈克
Welcome back to the Bar, Mike.
谢谢  哈维
Thanks, Harvey.
严格说  我还没进过
Technically, I wasn't really in.
-是  你从没真正有过资格  -是的呢
- Actually, you weren't really work in the Bar, ever. - Yeah.
我想问你今天过的怎么样
I'd ask how your day was,
但我上次问的时候  结果不太好
but last time I did that, it didn't go very well.
塔拉  我能跟你说实话吗
Tara, can I be honest with you?
当然  你可以跟我说任何事
Of course. You can tell me anything.
这是我们相互了解的一部分  我说过的
It's part of getting to know each other--I told you that.
我只是不确定你想不想听这个
Just not sure that this is what you had in mind.
路易  怎么了
Louis, what is going on?
那天
The other day,
我不想跟你说我为什么不高兴
when I didn't want to tell you what I was upset about,
我是在思考
I was trying to figure out
帮迈克・罗斯拿到律师资格的办法
a way to get Mike Ross into the Bar.
你是说在你们律所工作过的那个诈骗犯
You mean the fraud who worked at your firm?
说来话长  但我们是朋友  事情也过去了
It's a long story, but we're friends now and we're past it.
说来话长是什么意思
What do you mean it's a long story?
我是说迈克被捕前我就知道他的诈骗行为
I mean I knew Mike was a fraud before he was arrested.
我不仅知道
And I didn't just know.
我发现之后
When I found out about him,
不仅没有报案
instead of going to the police,
或者报告律师协会
or going to the Bar,
我还利用这事当上了冠名合伙人
I leveraged it to get my name on the wall.
塔拉  你说话呀
Tara, say something.
说什么
Say what?
你刚告诉我你发现了自己跟罪犯同事
You just told me you found out you were working with a criminal
却利用这信息升职
and you turned it into a promotion.
我知道  但你说我们要相互了解
I know that, but you said we should get to know each other.
你想要我说什么  路易
What do you want me to say, Louis?
我是说不知道你最喜欢的电影是什么
I didn't know what your favorite movie was.
或者你喜欢床的哪一边
Or what side of the bed you like.
但我以为至少我知道你的为人
But I thought at least I knew what kind of man you were.
塔拉  拜托
Tara, please.
这是我一生最羞愧的事
This is the thing I'm most ashamed aboutin my life
我告诉你是想让你知道
and I'm telling you to show you
我永远不会瞒你任何事
that I'm never gonna hide anything from you.
-或许你应该瞒  -什么
- Well, maybe you should hide some things from me. - What?
你听到了
You heard me.
是听到了
I heard you.
在我发现了你的事情之后
How dare you say that to me after
你怎么敢这样跟我说
what I had to find out about you.
这是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
意思是你坐在那儿
It means you're sitting there
说话好像你是最有道德的高等祭司
like you're the high priestess of moral authority,
可我们第一次上床时
when the first time we slept together,
你还跟别人好着呢
you were with another man.
你怎么能这么跟我说话
How can you say that to me?
那是我跟你  跟他都坦白的情况下
I was up front about it with you and with him.
你跟全世界都坦白了
You were up front about it with everybody
之后你想要我跟你坦白
and then you wanted me to be up front with you about things.
可你现在像看怪物一样看我
And now you're looking at me like I'm a monster!
好了  就这样吧
You know what? That's it.
就这样  你要去哪
That's it-- well, where are you going?
我回我的家睡
I'm sleeping at my place tonight.
塔拉  拜托
Look, Tara, please.
如果我知道你会是这个反应
If I knew that you were gonna react this way,
绝不会告诉你这些
I never would have told you any of this.
但你告诉我了  路易
But you did tell me, Louis.
-晚安  -塔拉  等等
- Good night. - Tara, wait.
我会给你打电话
I'll give you a call
等我想清楚之后
when I've had a chance to figure things out.